David Harrison

66 Grasslands Road, Tampa, Florida, 33674 d.harrison@youremail.com (123)456-7890

PROFIIF

Confident and highly experienced hospitality worker with 12 years of hotelier experience and a degree in Hospitality Management from the University of Central Florida. Impeccable customer service skills and a friendly yet professional communication manner Proven ability to run a hotel front desk, manage online booking systems, and oversee the management of five-star residences. Business and success-orientated work ethic and a track, record of improving customer satisfaction and team working efficiency. Excellent computer skills, including Microsoft Word and Outlook emails.

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Hotel Manager

Grand Hyatt Tampa Bay, Tampa, FL | March 2015 - February 2021

- Develop ideas for improving profit, including implementing a deals initiative which boosted winter profits by 15%
- Resolve customer complaints and answered client inquiries for 250-room complex
- Work alongside the sales and marketing team to ensure a holistic approach to the running of the hotel
- Oversee staff of 145, including desk clerks, cleaners, and lawn maintenance crew

Hotel Deputy Manager

Seminole Hard Rock Hotel, Tampa, FL | September 2011 - February 2015

- Created a customer retention plan, which increased the rate of returning customers by 25%
- Interviewed potential new additions to the department
- Maintained and updated the online CRM system
- Developed forecasts and reports

Front Desk Host

JW Marriott Tampa, Tampa, FL | March 2009 - August 2011

- Answered all incoming phone calls and emails
- Managed restaurant reservations
- Filed incident reports

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science In Hospitality Management UNIVERSITY OF CENTRAL FLORIDA Tampa, FL, September 2005 -September 2008

KEY SKILLS

- Impeccable customer service standards
- Proven problem-solving capability
- Computer literate
- Excellent organizational skills
- Strong ability to communicate effectively with the team and customers

CERTIFICATIONS

 Certified in Hotel Revenue Management by Cornell University, 2009